-海盗吗  -不  叫格林盆大雷区
- Pirates? - No. The Great Grimpen Minefield, they call it.
这样
Right.
不是你想的那样  那是巴斯克维尔试验场
It's not what you think. It's the Baskerville testing site.
有80多年了
It's been going for 80-odd years.
我估计没人知道里面到底有什么
I'm not sure anyone really knows what's there any more.
-炸弹吗  -不止是炸弹
- Explosives? - Not just explosives.
他们说闯进那地方
Break into that place and if you're lucky,
被炸死算走运的了
you just get blown up, so they say.
-免得你散步散到那边  -谢啦  我会记得
- In case you're planning a wee stroll. - Ta. I'll remember.
嗯  对旅游业有所影响
Aye. No, that buggers up tourism a bit,
多谢那条恶魔猎犬
so thank God for the demon hound.
-你看那节目了吗  那纪录片  -前不久看过
- Did you see that show? The documentary? - Quite recently, yeah.